어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
the Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예자 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi enters-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
when he'll become the world's
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise your spirit's sword high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled Martial Artist wanders Jipangu Country
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 칼의 소리가
An intense clash of swords
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Yesterday's battles makes you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Art! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 칼의 소리가
An intense clash of swords
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight your hardest with tranquility
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Art! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 빛나고 있었다 무사시!!
Shining brow! Musashi!
육도마왕 노부나가의 본거지를 찾아 세토 내해에 들어간 무사시 일행은
Musashi and others entered Seto Inland Sea to find the base of Nobunaga the Rikudomaoh,
오노고로 섬에 전해지는 우주인의 갑주를 손에 넣기 위해 범고래의 입에 진입, 불가사의한 팔찌를 손에 넣었다.
and then they entered into the Mouth of Orc to get the armor of aliens
handed down in Onogoro Island, and they got a mysterious ring.
그래서 현덕, 관우, 장비의 갑주와 뇌명환을 얻어 파워 업한 무사시 일행의 새로운 싸움이 시작된다.
Thus, with the armor of Gentoku, Kanu, and Chohi, they powered up and their new battles are about to begin.
파도타는 겐나이
발명왕이오
Surfing Gennai
is the Invention King
기분 좋다!
Feels good!
드디어 찾아냈구나, 무사시! 지금까지의 원한은 단단히 갚아줄 줄 알아라!
I finally found you, Musashi! You'll be paid back for everything you did to me!
화염탄 발사!
Launch Flame Bullets!
큰일이야! 괴물이! 괴물이 마을을!
This is bad! A monster! A monster is terrorizing the village!
뭣이!?
What!?
화재야, 화재다!
Fire! Fire!
메가톤성!
Megaton Castle!
젠장! 무슨 끔찍한 짓을!
Damn! What kind of cruel thing to do is that!?
무사시 씨! 큰일이야!
Mr. Musashi! This is bad!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
센히메 님이 없어. 찾아봐도 안 보여!
Senhime isn't there. I couldn't find her when I did!
-어?
-설마 메가톤성에...
-What?
-Could she be captured by Megaton Castle?
비켜비켜! 방해돼, 무사시! 어서 비켜!
Get out of my way! Musashi, you're standing in my way! Move!
센짱, 무사했소!
Sen-chan, you're safe!
센짱, 괜찮소? 어, 센짱?
Sen-chan, are you alright? Sen-chan?
꾸물대고 있지 말고 어서 불이나 꺼!
Don't be tardy and put off the fire!
알겠소!
Understood-dasu!
지라이얀은 어디에!
Where's Jiraiyan!?
모습이 안 보이오!
I can't find him-dasu!
이쪽이다! 허둥대지 말고 침착해라!
This way! Don't rush and calm down!
다들 잘 잡고 따라와!
Everyone, don't get lost!
우리 마을이...
Our village...
무슨 끔찍한 짓을!
How cruel of them!
마을 사람들이 잘못한 건 하나도 없는데.
The villagers didn't do anything wrong...
아무 죄도 없는 사람들을 이렇게 괴롭히고! 노부나가인지 코부나가(작은 붕어)인지 모르겠고 이 무사시는 절대 용서할 수 없소!
How dare they harass the people without crimes!? Nobunaga or Kobunaga(small fish), I, Musashi, cannot forgive-dasu!
야, 무사시!
Hey, Musashi!
-무사시 씨, 어디 가?
-무사시!
-Mr. Musashi, where are you going!?
-Musashi!
멈추시오, 메가톤성! 정정당당히 승부하시오!
Stop right there-dasu, Megaton Castle! Fight fair and square-dasu!
메가톤성, 어디 갔소?
Megaton Castle, where did you go-dasu?
어이, 정신 차려!
Hey, wake up!
바보! 멍청이! 얼간이! 바다에 가라앉은 메가톤성을 쫓을 수 있을 리가 없잖아!
Idiot! Fool! Dimwit! There is no way that you can possibly chase that Megaton Castle, sunk under the sea!
그만큼 무사시 씨의 분노는 깊어요!
It means that Mr. Musashi's anger is so deep!
그렇지만 어쨌든 바닷속에 들어갈 수 있는 탈것을 얻어야...
Anyway, still, we need a vehicle that can go inside water...
다만 대체 어떻게?
But, how?
그건 간단해!
That's simple!
발명가 겐나이 씨한테 부탁하면 어쩌면 만들어 줄 거야!
If you ask Mr. Gennai, an inventor, then he might make you one!
겐나이 씨?
Mr. Gennai?
정말 바다에 들어갈 수 있는 탈것을 만들 수 있소?
Can he really make a vehicle that can go inside the sea-dasu?
응. 별난 것만 골라서 발명하는 사람이니까 분명 만들어 줄 거야.
Yes. He's an inventor who always make some weird things, so he should make you one!
어? 이, 이게 겐나이 씨 집이야?
Huh? I- is this seriously Mr. Gennai's house?
왠지 재미있어 보이는 집이오!
This house looks interesting-dasu!
겐나이 씨! 겐나이 씨! 겐나이 씨?
Mr. Gennai! Mr. Gennai! Mr. Gennai?
-겐나이 님!
-겐나이 씨!
-Mr. Gennai!
집에 없는 것 같소.
It seems that he's not home-dasu.
아, 있다, 있다!
Hey, he's there!
어이, 겐나이 씨!
Hey, Mr. Gennai!
어? 저게 겐나이 씨야?
Huh? Is him Mr. Gennai?
겐나이 씨! 겐나이 씨!
Mr. Gennai! Mr. Gennai!
어이!
Hey!
겐나이 씨!
Mr. Gennai!
뭐냐, 켄타, 볼 일이라도?
What is it, Kenta? Do you need me?
실은  겐나이 씨에게 부탁할 게 있어서.
They had something to ask you, Mr. Gennai.
어라, 나한테 부탁이라고?
What? You have something to ask me?
저, 그게, 저희는 겐나이 씨 소문을 듣고...
Well, that is, we heard about you, Mr. Gennai...
내 소문을?
You heard about me?
그래그래그래그래. 어딜 봐도 괴짜에 성격 비뚤어진 할배로...
Yeahyeahyeahyeah! You're one old weirdo geezer with an extremely bad personality-
아, 아니, 천재적인 대발명가라는 소문을 들어서...
N- no, we heard that you're a great genius inventor!
그래, 천재라?
Genius, eh?
예. 어르신네 발명은 에도토피아에서도 평판이 좋습니다.
Yes. Your inventions are famous in Edotopia, too.
아이들부터 노인까지 모르는 자는 없을 정도로...
From children to old people, everybody knows you!
코지로도 능숙하오! 그런 놈, 들은 적도 없다고 말했잖소!
Kojiro, you're skillful-dasu! You said that you never heard of him-dasu!
너 닥치고 있어!
Shut up!
그러냐. 내 평판이 그렇게 널리 퍼진 것이냐.
I see. I am famous in many places, eh?
네!
Yes!
이야, 겐짱 부끄러워!
You're making Gen-chan embarrassed!
켄타가 마을에 돌아간 후에도 무사시 일행은 겐나이의 집에 남았다.
After Kenta went back to the village, Musashi and others stayed at Gennai's house.
그래, 내게 바다로 들어갈 수 있는 탈것, 즉 잠수함을 만들어 달라는 것이냐.
I see. You want me to make a vehicle that can go underwater, which is a submarine, right?
예. 지팡구국 전체에서 그런 걸 만들 수 있는 건 겐나이 님 밖에는 없습니다.
Yes. Only you, Mr. Gennai, can make such thing, in the whole Jipangu Country.
호오, 그런 소리를 들으니 기쁘구나.
I'm happy to hear that.
-부탁드려요!
-부탁드립니다!
-Please!
-We ask you!
그렇게까지 부탁한다면...
If you really want that much...
만들어 주시겠습니까!
Will you do it?
싫어.
No.
미안한데 난 부탁받으면 싫다고 하는 게 취미라서.
I'm sorry, but saying no when being asked is my hobby.
어이! 그거 만지면 안 돼!
Hey! Don't touch that!
그러니까 전기에 손대면 안 된다고 말했는데.
That's why I told you not to touch electricity.
부탁드립니다! 겐나이 님!
Please! Mr. Gennai!
-부탁드립니다!
-부탁드리오!
-Please!
-Please-dasu!
나는 변덕스러워서 누군가에게 뭔가를 부탁받아도 척척 받아주는 건 싫어.
I'm too whimsy to accept whoever's request so easily.
한 잔 더.
One more cup.
아, 네, 곧장!
Oh, got it!
이제 과일 먹고 싶다.
I want some fruits.
아, 네!
Oh, right!
책 읽고 싶어.
I want to read a book.
네!
Yes!
베개 있으면 좋겠어.
I want a pillow.
네!
Yes!
뱀장어 먹고 싶네.
I want to eat an eel.
네!
Yes!
등이 가려워.
My back is itchy.
네! 어딘가요?
Yes! To where?
TV 보고 싶어.
I want to watch television.
네!
Yes!
아, 기분 좋다.
This feels good.
오츠루도 센짱도 이제 됐소!
Both Otsuru and Sen-chan can quit-dasu!
이러니저러니 말하면서, 애초에 못 만드니까 속이고 있는 것이오!
He's just fooling around because he can't make one-dasu!
이런 놈, 대발명가가 아니고 그냥 파도나 타는 할배일 뿐이오!
This guy cannot possibly a great inventor, but instead, he's just an old geezer who happens to surf-dasu!
뭐, 뭔 소리를 지껄이는 거야, 무사시!
W- what the heck are you saying, Musashi!?
꼬맹아, 날 파도타는 할배라고 부른 건 네가 처음이다. 좋아, 너희 중 하나라도 저 파도에 탈 수 있는 놈이 있다면 생각해 보지.
Kiddo, you're the first one to call me a surfing geezer.
Well then, if even one of you can surf on that waves, then I'll think about it.
아니, 나, 산에서 자라서...
Well, I was born in mountain-dasu...
어라? 쥬베 씨는?
What about you, Mr. Jube?
나는 최근 살이 쪄서.
I became fat recently.
코지로!
Kojiro!
나, 나도 최근 빈혈 증상이...
I- I'm suffering from anemia recently...
내가 할게.
I'll do it.
센짱!
Sen-chan!
센짱! 부탁하오!
Sen-chan! Please do it-dasu!
헤, 역시 서핑은 수영복 입은 여자얘가 어울려.
Heh, surfing is beautiful when done by a girl in swimsuit.
게다가 하이레그, 견딜 수가 없어!
Moreover, high-legs! This is the best!
그래도 혼자서는 왠지 허전한데.
But only one doesn't look complete...
아무리 하이레그라도, 혼자서는... 둘이라면 나, 왠지 더 할 기분이 들 지도...
Even for a high-leg, one isn't enough... Maybe I'll feel more like doing it if there are two...
저, 그거라면 저도.
For that, I can do it...
아, 그래, 그래!
Oh, I see, I see!
아, 안 되오, 오츠루!
N- no way-dasu, Otsuru!
나, 할 거야, 무사시 씨! 센히메 님에게 질 수 없어.
I'll do it, Mr. Musashi! I can't lose to Senhime!
어? 그, 그래도, 오츠루...
Huh? B- but, Otsuru...
조금이라도 무사시 씨에게 도움이 되고 싶어.
I want to be helpful, Mr. Musashi.
오츠루...
Otsuru...
나는 이게 할 수 있는 최대한이지만...
This is all I can do...
노스탤직! 이게 또 물에 젖으면 모양이 나오겠어. 참을 수가 없군!
Nostalgic! It'll be a perfect appearance when she gets wet in water! I can't believe this!
몸에 착 달라붙어 선이 나오다니, 이야...
The clothes will stick to the body and the lines will show up...
내가 무슨 소리 했나?
Did I say something?
뭐, 그런 갸륵한 정성이 마음에 들었다. 나도 남자. 잠수함을 만들어 주겠다.
I like your brave attitude. I am a man too. I'll make a submarine for you.
점잔빼지 마시오, 이 변태 할배 꼴불견!
Don't put on airs-dasu, you perverted old geezer! How unsightly!
어라?
Huh?
과연 잠수함은 가능한가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Will the submarine even be made? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
by Subdivers
잠수함 따위는 요리를 만드는 것보다 간단해!
Making a submarine is easier than cooking!
겐나이 씨!
Mr. Gennai!
오츠루 왔어! 쉬자!
Otsuru's here! Let's take a break!
네에!
Yeah!
아야!
Ouch!
아이고, 손가락이야, 손가락!
Ow, my finger! My finger!
건강한 할배이오.
What an energetic old man-dasu.
그래도 겐나이 씨한테 맡겨도 정말 괜찮을지...
But, can we really trust on Mr. Gennai-dasu?
그 외에 부탁할 만한 사람은 없으니까요.
It's not like there is someone that we can ask.
내 칼은 톱이나 도끼가 아니다.
My sword is not a saw or an ax.
어이, 목재가 부족해!
Hey, there aren't enough lumbers!
아, 네, 곧장 갈게요!
R- right! I'll be there soon!
내 손으로 만들면 이렇게 되지. 이 디자인, 이 모습. 어딜 봐도 천재적이라고밖에 설명할 길이 없구만.
This is what my inventions look like. Look at its design and its form. It's completely brilliant.
왠지 눈이 튀어나온 금붕어 같군요.
It looks like a pop-eyed goldfish.
어라, 뭐라고?
Oh, what did you say?
아, 아니아니, 정말 완벽합니다, 네!
N- no, no, it's truly excellent, yes!
어서 메가톤성을 쫓소!
Let's chase Megaton Castle right away-dasu!
그럼 갔다 오겠소!
Then, see you later-dasu!
너무 무리하지 마, 무사시 씨.
Don't overdo it, Mr. Musashi.
아, 나도 가고 싶다.
I want to go with them.
잘 있어라! 선물 가져...
Have a nice trip! Bring some present-
뭔 소리야! 당신도 가!
What are you saying? You're going with them!
어라, 나도?
What, me too?
당연하잖소! 겐나이 씨 외에 대체 누가 조종하오!
It's obvious-dasu! Who'll pilot this, else than Mr. Gennai-dasu?
자, 어서.
Come on.
수상해. 뭔가 숨기고 있는 거지?
You're suspicious. You're hiding something, aren't you?
아니, 나, 내가 만든 배에 탈 용기 따위 없어.
Er, no, I don't have courage to ride in a ship that I made.
뭐, 뭐, 조종 방법은 안에 사용 설명서가 있으니까 괜찮을 거야.
Well, there's a manual inside, so that you can learn how to operate!
정말 지멋대로이오...
You're really irresponsible-dasu...
잘 부탁해, 다들!
Do your best, everyone!
무사시 씨! 조심해!
Mr. Musashi! Be careful!
뭐, 뭣이오, 이 좁은 건...
T- this is so narrow-dasu...
저예산이니까 어쩔 수 없잖아. 어디, 이게 이래서, 이건가.
It was low-cost, so deal with it. Now, this will do this, and this...
아, 가라앉는다, 가라앉아! 대성공이다! 만세!
It's sinking, it's sinking! It's success! Hooray!
잠깐. 가라앉기만 해서는 그냥 침몰선이잖아. 떠올라야 잠수함이지.
Wait. If it just sinks, then it's just a sinking ship. It's a submarine when it floats back up.
만약 무사시 씨 일행이 못 돌아오면 어떻게 되는지 알죠?
You know what will happen to you if they don't make it back, right?
아, 네, 그게...
R- right, of course...
우와! 예쁘오!
Wow! How beautiful-dasu!
우린 물고기가 되었소.
We became a fish-dasu.
들떠 있을 때가 아니야!
It's not the time to be festive!
이 넓은 바닷속에서 메가톤성을 찾는 것이니 꽤나 시간이 걸릴 지도 모릅니다.
Since we're finding Megaton Castle in this wide sea, it will take a while.
어, 레이더에 반응이!
There's a reaction on the radar!
메가톤성이오?
Is it Megaton Castle-dasu?
몰라. 그래도 꽤나 크다.
I don't know. But it's pretty big.
저것이오.
That's it-dasu.
어? 저건!
Huh? That must be...
지라이얀!
Jiraiyan!
지라이얀 님입니까?
Mr. Jiraiyan?
저 놈, 모습이 안 보인다 했더니 이런 곳에서 스쿠버다이빙이나 하고 있었어.
We couldn't find him because he was scuba diving at a place like this...
해설해 보자. 왜 지라이얀이 수중에서 아무렇지도 않는지 말하자면, 두루마기를 공기통 대신 쓰고 있기 때문이다.
Let me explain why is Jiraiyan perfectly fine in waters. It's because he's using the roll as an air tank.
무사시!
Musashi!
뭐라뭐라? 우리도 함께 가오. 인가...
What, what? We are following, -dasu, eh?
따라오라 했소.
He's telling us to follow him-dasu.
좋아!
Great!
지금이야!
Now!
뭔 일이냐!
What's going on!?
하방에서 어뢰 공격을 받은 것 같습니다!
It seems that we're attacked with torpedoes from below!
뭐야!?
What!?
철저하게 혼내 주고 바다의 물고기밥으로 만들어 버려라!
Punish them thoroughly and make them into scraps of seaweed!
뭐야, 이건?
What's this?
어이, 하지 마, 케로키치!
Hey, don't do that, Kerokichi!
으악! 이대로라면 바다의 큰실말(모즈쿠)가 되고 마오!
Wah! We'll end up becoming seaweeds(mozuku)-dasu!
물고기밥(모쿠즈)이다, 멍청아!
It's scraps of seaweed(mokuzu), you dimwit!
오, 잘 하오, 코지로! 장인!
You're great, Kojiro! What artisanship!
그러나 이대로라면 당하는 건 시간의 문제입니다.
But it's only a matter of time before we get hit.
그래. 분명 이럴 때를 위한 비밀 병기가 있다고 했을 터.
Right. There's supposedly a secret weapon here, for the times of need.
이거다!
This is it!
이게...
This...?
비밀 병기.
Secret weapon.
정말! 이렇게 된 바 자포자기다!
Damn! Anything goes now!
뭐, 뭐냐, 저건!
W- what's that!?
곧장 이 쪽으로 오고 있습니다!
It's heading toward here directly!
회피해라! 전속으로 회피!
Evade! Evade at full speed!
시간이 부족합니다!
There's not enough time!
이자식! 이자식! 이자식! 이자식!
You bastard! You bastard! You bastard! You bastard!
뭐야? 무사시 놈들이 이 메가톤성 속에?
What!? Musashi bastards came into this Megaton castle!?
예! 제 3 통로로 이동중입니다!
Yessir! They are heading to the 3rd pathway!
애송이가. 이 내가 직접 처리해 주겠다!
You brat! I'll get rid of you myself!
이천일류 섬광권!
Nitenichiryu: Flash Sword!
흥. 사냥감이 굳이 찾아오다니, 찾는 수고를 덜었구나.
Hmph. How grateful of my prey, to save the trouble of finding one.
용서할 수 없소! 아무 죄도 없는 마을 사람들을 괴롭히다니!
You are unforgivable-dasu! How dare you trouble the villagers who didn't do anything wrong!?
그래라, 지껄여라! 여기가 네놈들의 무덤이다!
Yeah, say all what you want! This place will be your grave!
흥, 큰소리는 뻥뻥 치더니. 날 상대하기에는 아직 10년 정도 이른 모양이구나.
Hmph. All bark and no bite? It seems that you're 10 years too early to face me.
돌아가서 엄마네 젖이라도 빨아라.
Go back and drink your mother's milk.
이게, 어른이라고 아이를 바보 취급하다니 용서할 수 없소!
Even for adults, treating children like a fool is unforgivable-dasu!
카라쿠리 변화!
Karakuri Shift!
겐토쿠 아머!
Gentoku Armor!
네놈, 그런 갑주를 가지고 있었느냐.
How dare you brat have an armor like that!?
이천일류 섬광검!
Nitenichiryu: Flash Sword!
이대로라면 침몰한다! 출력을 늘려 부상해라!
We'll sink at this rate! Increase output and rise!
동력실! 풀 파워다!
Power Room! Full power!
도쿠간류, 각오하시오!
Dokuganryu, prepare yourself-dasu!
쌍두의 용!
Double-Headed Dragon!
무사시!
Musashi!
무사시 님!
Mr. Musashi!
승부는 일단 나중이다!
We'll finish this later!
멈추시오!
Stop-dasu!
뭐, 뭐야!?
W- what's going on!?
기다리시오!
Wait-dasu!
멈추시오, 메가톤성!
Stop-dasu, Megaton Castle!
좋아, 케로키치! 고!
Alright, Kerokichi! Go!
살았다.
We live...
고맙소, 케로키치!
Thank you, Kerokichi!
그래도 아깝네요. 기껏 메가톤성 안까지 들어갔는데.
Still, it was so close. We went into Megaton Castle...
뭐, 그만큼 피해를 주었으니.
Well, we gave a lot of damage.
그래도 기껏 만들어 받은 잠수함을 잃어버렸소.
But, we lost the submarine that we just got-dasu...
잘 됐소. 다시 오츠루의 수영복 차림을 보여야만 할 참이었소.
What a relief-dasu. Otsuru might had to show her swimsuit look again-dasu.
그래도 쪼끔 아쉽고...
But then again, that's kind of unfortunate-dasu...
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
오츠루!
Otsuru!
봐라, 내가 말한 대로 무사하게 돌아왔잖아?
Look. They came back safely, just as I told you!
그래도 잠수함이 부서진 것 같은데.
But it seems that the submarine is broken.
아니아니, 그런 시시한 건 일단 아무래도 좋잖아?
Hey, isn't that good enough for now?
엉망진창 노인 겐나이에게 휘둘리면서도, 메가톤성에 과감하게 덤빈 무사시 일행. 적의 우두머리 노부나가는 어디에 있는가?
Even while being abused by Gennai, a weird old geezer, Musashi and others challenged their way to Megaton Castle.
Where is Nobunaga, the boss of their enemy?
메가톤성의 기지는? 비밀의 핵심에 다가가는 다음 이야기를 기다려라!
Where is the base of Megaton Castle? Wait for the next story when they'll discover the core of the secret!
싸우고 맞았어
I fought and I got beaten
코피 쓩이야 랑데부
Nosebleed drips rendezvous
나도 지지 않으려 한발!
I can't lose, so take my blow!
핀치 펀치로 대역전
Pinch! Punch! I won by reversal
다음 시간 즐거운
Next is delightful lunchtime
급식일 텐데
But it's not delightful today
선생님의 벼락이
The thunder of my teacher
나한테만 떨어져 왔어
only hit me and nobody else
사정을 말해도
I tried to explain
들어주지 않는 채
But he won't listen
어떻게 해도 역시
Now whatever I do
눈물이 나오고 말아
I end up crying
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
왠지 안타까워
you'll feel downhearted
우리는 겐나이 씨의 잠수함으로 바닷속을 탐색해, 적의 본거지를 찾아내었소.
Using Mr. Gennai's submarine, we found the base of the enemy in the deep sea-dasu.
그러나 그쪽의 방어는 엄해서 가까이 다가가기가 꽤나 어렵소.
But because their defenses are strict, it's difficult to approach-dasu.
거기서 코지로가 생각해낸 게 봉제인형으로 변장한다는 작전!
And there, Kojiro suggested a plan to disguise using stuffed toy!
그러나 정말 이런 걸로 잘 될지 모르겠소.
But, I'm not sure about this-dasu...
다음 이야기! 큰 웃음거리 문어 춤 작전이오
Next story! Big Laughter Octopus Dance Strategy
질풍노도의 문어회이오!
It's a stormy raw octopus-dasu!
다음 이야기
큰 웃음거리
문어 춤 작전이오
재미있게 보세요!
Next Story
Big Laughter
Octopus Dance Strategy
We hope you enjoy!